smartlation.com 2017-06-06

# S

                                          - 1 -
                     SMARTLATION LTD. - PRIVACY POLICY
Smartlation Ltd. ("Smartlation") is committed to protecting your privacy and your
personally identifiable information ("Personal Information").
Smartlation has created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to let you know what
information Smartlation (or others on its behalf) collect from you when you use of
Smartlation platform ("Platform") and the services contained and provided through
the Platform ("Services"), how is this information collected and how is it used.
This Privacy Policy is part of and should be read in conjunction with the Terms and
Conditions. When you access or use Smartlation's website, the Platform, utilize or
provide Services through the Platform, you agree that Smartlation (or others on its
behalf) may collect, use and disclose your information (including Personal
Information) in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
Smartlation (or others on its behalf) collects and stores the Personal Information from
you, including without limitation, your name, home or other physical address, email
address, phone number, other contact information, domain names and other
information relating to your website and you webpage. Smartlation also collects and
stores an activity log unique to you that collects certain administrative and traffic
information including without limitation source IP address, time of access, date of
access, web page(s) visited, language use, Platform crash reports, type of browser
used, the technical operation of the Platform, and any information required to ensure
your use of the Platform is compliant with the Terms and Conditions. Smartlation
collects and stores the aforesaid information when you visit its website; use the
Platform, receive or provide Services through the Platform and also in your
communications with Smartlation.
You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of your Personal Information and all
other information you submit to Smartlation (or to others on its behalf). Inaccurate
information will affect the information you receive when using Smartlation's website,
the Platform and Smartlation's ability to contact you as contemplated in this Privacy
Policy as well as to provide you with the Platform content in the best manner possible.
USE OF INFORMATION
Smartlation uses the Personal Information and other information it (or others on its
behalf) collect from or about you to make the Platform available for you, to provide
translation services using Services Providers, to conduct statistical analysis, to provide
customer support, to undertake necessary security and identify verification checks, to
process any of your online transactions, meet certain business requirements and for
any other purpose related, directly or indirectly, to the operation of the Platform.
Smartlation may disclose your Personal Information (and any other information) to
any third parties that provide services to Smartlation in order to allow enable or
improve the provision of the Services to you. Your Personal Information may also be
used by Smartlation to provide you with promotional offers and information regarding
Smartlation's as well as products and services from third parties carefully selected by
us and in order for Smartlation to improve the Platform, the customer services and
services provided through the Platform. Smartlation may also use the aforesaid

                                           - 2 -
information to track your use of Smartlation's website and the Platform and/or for
other internal purposes, such as evaluating, providing, and improving the website and
the Platform.
Smartlation may disclose your Personal Information to associated entities and/or to
third parties, at Smartlation's sole discretion, where the purpose of such disclosure is
to provide you with the Services. In addition, Smartlation may disclose your Personal
Information and other information collected, if required to do so by law, or if
Smartlation believes in good faith that such action is necessary to comply with
applicable legislation, a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process, or
to protect and defend Smartlation's rights or property, the personal safety of other
users of the Platform or the public at large. Smartlation reserves the right to share the
aforesaid information with appropriate authorities and financial institutions, if
Smartlation determines in its sole discretion that you are attempted to defraud
Smartlation or if Smartlation suspects you are committing any fraudulent activity or
any other prohibited transaction or any criminal activity or if you publish hate speech
on your website or if you breach the Terms and Conditions.
CHOICE / OPT-OUT
By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you hereby allow Smartlation to provide you with
communications from Smartlation itself, as well as from third parties, either in
connection with the Platform or the Services or in connection with other (including,
but not limited to, commercial matters and offers). You hereby acknowledge and
consent to the sending of such communications, and will not argue that such activity
amounts to sending of unsolicited communications. You also hereby acknowledge that
Smartlation are not responsible for the communication sent to you by third parties,
their content and method of distribution.
You may opt-out from receiving communications from Smartlation by sending a
blank e-mail to us with the word "Remove" to admin@smartlation.com and/or by
clicking the unsubscribe link on our e-mails sent to you.
COOKIES
Smartlation uses a browser feature known as cookies, which are small text files which
are placed on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages, to
track your activities, record your preferences, and make our site and the Platform
more responsive to your needs by delivering a better and more personalized
experience to you.
SECURITY
Smartlation has implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures
to protect and safeguard the Personal Information under its control from unauthorized
access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or
accidental loss. All of Smartlation's employees and data processors that have access
to, and are associated with the processing of your Personal Information, are obliged to
respect the confidentiality of your Personal Information.

                                           - 3 -
LINKS TO OTHER SITES
The Platform and Smartlation's website may contain links to other sites. Other sites
may also reference or link to the Platform. Smartlation is not responsible for the
privacy practices or the content of such other online websites, and any information
collected by these third party online sites is not governed by this Privacy Policy, and
Smartlation assumes no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the policies
(including privacy policies), practices, actions or omissions of such third parties.
TRANSFER
In the event that Smartlation sells, assigns or transfers some or all of its business or
assets to a successor or acquirer, or if Smartlation is acquired by or merge with a third
party, or if Smartlation files for bankruptcy or becomes insolvent, Smartlation may
sell, assign or transfer all of your Personal Information and other information provided
by you or about you, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer.
DISCLAIMER
The Platform operate "AS-IS" and "AS-AVAILABLE", without liability of any kind.
Smartlation is not responsible for events beyond its direct control. Smartlation cannot
guarantee nor do it represent that there will be error-free performance regarding the
privacy of your Personal Information, and Smartlation will not be liable for any
indirect, incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to the use or release of
Personal Information.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS POLICY
By agreeing to the Terms and Conditions during the registration process on
Smartlation's website, or by using or browsing the Platform, you agree to be bound by
this Privacy Policy, and to any changes Smartlation may make to this Privacy Policy
from time to time – without the need to notify you about such changes. It is
recommended that you revisit this Privacy Policy regularly so as to be kept apprised
of the updated Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Platform and/or receipt of
Services following changes to this Privacy Policy mean you accept these changes.
